Homework week 6
Given a computer network with n nodes and m edges. Your task is to write a program to :
1.	Visit all nodes of the network by BFS
2.	Visit all nodes of the network by DFS using recursion
3.	Visit all nodes of the network by DFS using stack structure.
4.	Compute the number connected components in the network

The network is given in a text file “network.inp” as described below:
-	The first line contains two integer numbers n and m
-	m following lines each contains two numbers u,v indicating that there is an undirected edge between u and v.


Dòng đầu tiên là 2 số nguyên n, m tương ứng số đỉnh, cạnh
M dòng tiếp theo thể hiện cho cạnh
n <= 1000
m <= 1000000
Input: network.inp
Output  ra màn hình
Thăm theo số thứ tự các đỉnh từ bé đến lớn
